Like, I just need to understand. Let me understand. Let me understand how so many people
constantly say, what is the solution? What are we going to do? How are we going to get out of this?
And then still say, but we don't need any assistance from individuals who have actually
been in this. Can somebody, help me understand. Help me understand. Because it don't make no sense.
Like, do they not understand like the severity of where we are, of the extreme, the extremity,
extremity, the extreme situation that we're in, like the extremism. Do they not, is seeing the
kidnapping of the kids not enough? Is, is seeing the, the, the vaccines being taken out of schools,
like is seeing the, the, the, the taking the blackness out to museums? Like, is it, is that not
enough? Did y'all not go in on job? If you are against fascism, if you are against America,
and by the way, they can make anything fit these definitions, then they are considering you
criminal. So I'm trying to understand what is the, what is the plan? You've absolved that you
empowered, that you continue to support with your taxpayer money. You've absolved them of any
responsibility, both professionally and privately. Are you absolving your neighbors too? Like, I'm,
I'm just trying to figure out like who would have to do anything to help protect the citizens of
this country. Let me know because I'm, I'm, I'm still trying to get it. I'm still trying to
understand, still trying to understand this logic, this logic. I'm still trying to understand this
logic. You, it's, it's not, it is so nonsensical to state that in this extreme time of dire, that
individuals who have served at the highest levels of office in this country have no responsibility
to the people of this country. Quiet, pay attention, and you will get contact. I'm talking. I'm just,
I'm trying to, then we have someone here. You want to sound smart. So bad. About why does that man owe
you money? Stop taking care of men, Amanda? Which man are you talking about? Because I can name free
men that owe me money. What does stop taking care of men have to do with men owing me money? Like,
I'm trying to understand it. Again, again, I have no idea. And it's not all bots because I've seen
people I know say, well, it's not Obama's job. It's not Kamala's job. Yes, it is. It is all of our job
talking about. It's everyone's job. One's job. Do y'all not? Community is. How did y'all not? And it's
not a job. You get paid for it in safety. You get paid for it in futures for your children. You get paid
for it in literally peace. Goons right here said it's our only true job to figure out how to live
peacefully with each other. That is our only job. And we're going to have to push through people who
have made it their job to exploit us. And that has been happening over and over and over and over again,
because so often what happens is people start out as us, then they level up and then they say,
oh, I don't want to go back to that. And they join in the exploitation. And so many here on my Instagram
go along with this. So many on low vibrational threads go along with this. It's not their job.
Hey, it's not my job. And I don't even like that anywhere. I don't like it's not my job anywhere,
because it really is some capitalist, individualist, imperialist crap. It's not my job. So you only do
things if you're getting paid for them. Like it's, it's silly. It's silly. The post I made about Obama
in Chicago is to remind you that as the city that made that man is on Ireland smiling, Obama should be
waking up every fucking day. In my opinion, sending out good luck, Chicago messages. We should have been
seen Obama on Instagram live or some shit with Brandon. The least these people can do is use
their platforms. They may not have to put their body on the line. They all the folks, I get that.
But the least they can do is use their platforms. And y'all be on my head about my platform. Every
goddamn get healthcare from the taxpayers. I don't get Secret Service protection from the
taxpayers. I didn't put us in this bullshit. But y'all got these folks just able to, what?
Like duped the great and a jackass here will say, well, if you voted for Kamala, there wouldn't be
troops in Chicago. And I will continue to repeat what I have to say. Because everything I'm saying
makes sense. And someone said, I don't know why you try with these people. Because one thing I know
from my therapist is that change is nonlinear and that it is not the same for everybody and that it
takes time. One thing I learned from the great revolutionary Thomas Sankara is that as one,
you're going to have to repeat yourself over and over and over again. You're going to have to repeat
yourself over and over and over again. Speaking of Sankara, this is my cat Sankara.
This is facts. There's really no way around it. So I've had to get much better about repeating
myself. And when y'all say, well, black men and black women, we've really sacrificed. So we don't
need to be involved. That's stupid. It's dumb. It's dumb. That's an idiotic thought process.
Because it in no way has anything to do with reality.
None. None. Unless you're going to leave. Unless you're going to leave. It has nothing to do with
reality. So I don't know why y'all think that that's a logical thought process. Like, what do you,
how do you think that turns out for you? How do you think that turns out for you? And yes,
all the women who have said that have gotten very mad at me for saying it's dumb. I don't care.
I don't care. I consider that to be wildly illogical and completely out of line, out of alignment with
our ancestry. Uh, it is completely impractical and it literally has nothing factually to do with
history. Will I interview Kamala? Kamala would never do an interview with me. Kamala Harris would
never do an interview with me. She wouldn't because one thing I'm not going to do is have the questions
submitted. And that is something that she does. The questions are submitted ahead of time. People
are told what they can and can't ask, what they can and can't say. And then she pulls the black mama
neck roll and then people get scared and shut down. Remember when, um, Charlemagne was like,
so who's the leader of the democratic party? Joe Biden or Joe Manchin? And she was like,
how dare you say that? How dare you? And she still ain't say shit. She still didn't say shit.
She just did the posturing, right? Because the black identity politics is weaponized. So she did
the posturing. It got shut down. And you know what? The question was not answered. But guess what?
Joe Manchin absolutely was a fake Democrat, then switched over to independent after he stood in
the way of all of these very important, uh, votes. Now, by the way, I'm going to go on a book tour.
And when I go on a book tour, I would, I can't wait to hear people try and say,
you are mad at, because you know, they're going to try it. You know, they're going to try it. Mind you,
my book is actually about where we are. My book is actually grounded in connecting us to community
and alignment and reminding us of where we come from and who we come from so we can know where
we're going. When I was in college, I started reading James Baldwin's The Fire Next Time. Hold on.
Look at how tattered. Look at how tattered this is. Look at how tattered this is. And it's tattered and
highlighted because we need words and writing to carry us through. We need it. And so I said, well,
I had it given to me for my time. So I need to put it down for our time. You understand me?
I'm going to read some from here. It is not too much to say that whoever wishes to become a truly
moral human being and let us not ask whether or not this is possible. I think we must believe that
it is a possibility must first divorce himself from all the prohibitions, crimes, and hypocrisies of
the Christian church. If the concept of God has any validity or any use, it can only be to make us
larger, freer, and more loving. If God cannot do this, then it is time we got rid of him. That's
highlighted. I love you. I love you too. I love you three. I love you four. Here's another one. Notes of a
Native Son is my other one. Jordi, please. Please, Jordi. I'm busy. Now, I want to remind y'all that I did
just put a drop on my store, AmandaLand Exports. So those of you who watch Views from AmandaLand,
we have Views from AmandaLand notebooks, sticker sheets. We have a vocabulary, a word vocablog,
etc. All designed by my hand. Okay? All designed by my hand. This is not stuff that like I sent off to
somebody to design and then put it out. I designed it. The book comes out November 8th. What would the
ancestors say comes out November 8th? Thank you, Hema. Hema bought a bundle. There's also pins,
all the things. But I came on here to just remind you, will the vocablog have suggested words? It
has a list of resistance vocabulary. Yes. There's a list of resistance vocabulary on the front page,
on the inside page. But the point of it is for you to watch the show and log your vocab words every
week. So again, it's all of our job. We are each other's business. We are each other's business.
It is all of our job to wake up and provide whatever we have for that day towards protecting
each other. It's not the same every day. It's not. Some days you have more than others. It's not.
And I get it. That's why we have community. So that everybody doesn't have to be exhausting
everything every day. Community at large is just, uh, the black community at large is poisoned soil.
And that's how I feel about that. Will my book only be available on my website? Uh, at first,
but then it will be available on different, um, independent bookstore sites.
So I'm in the process. You all have a fabulous evening. Remember, um, who is representing the black
community? What does that even mean? I don't know what, I, sorry, I lost you five exclamation points
means, but that doesn't, I said what I said. The black community at large is poisoned soil.
And those who follow me and who've listened to my, my, my speaking, who read my work,
they know, they know exactly what I mean. So if you want to, if you want to understand what I mean,
you're going to have to stick around and actually like consume my content, not just pop in and get
tidbits. Cause I'm not that girl. I'm not, I'm not this influencer content that y'all are used to.
I'm in long form. I look at the world long form. I look at my life long form. My commentary is long
form. I am not speaking in, um, you know, sound bites that are not able to be strung together.
I'm in continuous thought. So you can't just pop in. I'm not a, I'm not a sitcom from the 90s where
we have a beginning and an end every episode. I'm like Grey's Anatomy. This shit don't never end.
This shit don't never end. Different characters come in, come out, niggas die. But we keep going.
We keep, we keep going. The story continues. The story continues. So if you really trying to
understand or see me as a resource, know that you have to engage with my content.
You can't sip it. You can't dabble in it. You have to engage in it. So
Sorry, I'm just ignoring dumb questions. Damn. Someone said some of us been here since George
died on Grey's Anatomy and I, I, I felt that right here. But can we take it back to Denny?
Do you even know, have we been here since then? Have we been here since Izzy and Denny?
Someone said, I support Jasmine Crockett and Kamala Harris. I gotta go.
A dumb question. A dumb question is asking me why or when, or if I run for office.
That's a dumb question. It's a dumb question. So I just, I think, I think the fact that folks
think that they can simultaneously mourn Asada without mourning her politics volumes to where
we are. I think y'all like the Black Panthers for the aesthetic. You don't even know shit about the
Black Panthers, but you like the look of it all. You know, like Swiss and Alicia dressing up as Black
Panthers for Halloween, but not saying shit about Palestine, even though the Black Panthers were
absolutely involved in the movement for liberation in Palestine. I think y'all, y'all like Beyonce dressing
folks up for formation and, and presenting the Black Panthers as a pageantry, as a, as a, as a piece of
performance, as curated costumes without acknowledging that those costumes were once uniforms that let
everybody know what you were, what you were about before you opened your mouth, which made you
simultaneously a pillar of your community and a target. And not enough of y'all understand that.
So it makes sense to you to say, rest in peace Asada, I stand for Kamala Harris. When those are so
deeply disparate, okay, deeply disparate. So let's dig beneath the surface. Let's dig beneath the surface so we
can really begin to understand what we are. Cause a lot of folks is really out here just
being on the surface, which is why it's so easy for you to be poisoned and indoctrinated because there's
so little, there's so little depth for the shit to seek through. And it doesn't have to stay that way.
It doesn't have to stay that way. It gets deeper by you creating depth.
Wasalu, please call me. I want to talk to you and I miss you. Please call me. So let's cut the shit.
Let's stop with the posturing. Let's thank you. Let's stop with the posturing y'all.
Again, like I've been saying, like I end all my shows with, we are each other's business. When we
look out for each other, we lift each other up. For the record, I've always been this person. You
see what you see Lupe here. He will tell you she's always been this type of nigga from day one.
Lupe met me when I was what? 22? So, and just please give Was, please, sorry. Please give Lupe
his props because he was talking about Palestine before niggas even was really on the wave like
that. And there's always been repercussions for talking about Palestine. Always. I didn't
experience it till later, but that nigga was on it. So, you know, that's the type of shit that I feel
like y'all don't really understand. You said when I said Lupe, I am. I am talking about
Lupe Fiasco. He's in the chat. I don't think enough people understand that just speaking
requires bravery in a nation that has always been fascist. This nation has always been fascist.
It's just at a new level of fash. We're at high fascism, like high fashion. We're at high fascism
now. So nothing, someone asked what happened with me and Tamir Rice's mom. Nothing, nothing
happened with me and Tamir Rice's mom. That is a very aggrandized story. That is a misrepresentation
of what actually happened on the internet. Basically, Black Pages had started to push a narrative
that she was accusing Sean King and Tamika Mallory of stealing money from her. And the pages that were
posting this were all Black Pages, like the Griot, the Root, etc. However, there was no journalism.
There was no evidence in there. It was just making this statement, which I thought was really sus
because I'm like, again, the fascism, the COINTELPRO, I'm like, nobody finds it odd that all of these
pages just jumped in on discrediting these folks that have dedicated their lives to speaking on behalf
of Black communities that are facing police violence. And I was like, y'all know I don't fuck with
Sean King. However, I just think it is very libelous and dangerous. And people said that I was attacking
her by stating this. And I'm sure I could have written it with a bit more clarity. However, I was
not attacking her. And for what it's worth, it was revealed that they had not stolen money from her.
But of course, the truth is never as amplified as the accusation. And I think it's really
important that these types of things be questioned because it's very easy to simply just discredit
people without any merit. I am somebody who has been discredited very consistently with no merit.
I'm still being accused of saying that I lied about a nigga sexually assaulting me, which I never did.
Never did. Never did. And now we watch Israel just lie every all day, every single day
and discredit everybody. So, you know, I think that it's, um, I think that it's really,
it's just far too easy on this internet to just say things. And I've been, I mean, I've been,
trust me, I've been guilty of this as well to just say things without, you ain't never lied with my
five closings to just say things without actually having, um, tent poles to stand on that legitimize
them. And I don't think it is, I think it's irresponsible. And I've been the victim of this as
well. All those black art, all those black websites, write articles about Amanda is unlikable and nobody
had met me before. So, um, you know, civility is dead, not where I live. My neighborhood is incredibly
civil. And you know, civility was dead when I lived in LA, but where I live, I have reattacked,
I have reconnected with civility where people will let you cross the street, even though the light is
green, right? Where, where, where people will, um, hold the door for you. People, if it's raining and
you don't have an umbrella, people will come back. Who is Keandria? That's the thing. Y'all be naming
people that I don't even know exist and they have smoke for me. I don't even know who these people are,
but they are existing every day with me on their mind. Mind you, I'm in here singing show tunes with
my cats. You understand? Like it's, it's Sunday. Imagine having smoke for me and I'm in here like
silver and gold, silver and gold. I'd rather have Jesus than silver and gold.
Like imagine, imagine what she could have to say about me and Tamir Rice's mom. There is no me and
Tamir Rice's mom. I have never spoken about her. Uh, I have, I mean, spoken to her. I've never met her.
They're accusing me of attacking her. I never attacked her. I said, I think that it's kind of
crazy that these pages are posting her accusations without any supported evidence.
And I don't think there's anything wrong with making that statement. What do you think about
people coming for democratic candidates in an election year? I think that your context and
your perspective needs to shift coming for democratic candidates is simply making demands of
candidates. And for the record, every single community does this. You make demands, earn your
boat. You make demands. Black people. I'm killing Mike was like, I'm not Republican or Democrat. I'm just
whoever's going to give us what we want. And when he said it, I remember being very annoyed by that.
I'm being like, he's a, ah, now I'm not saying there haven't been other things that made me be
like, but in that particular context, I was wrong. And I'm not saying that I was wrong because I'm a
Republican, but I understand now his sentiment of we shouldn't be aligned with any party.
Right? Like I get it now. We shouldn't be aligned with any party because neither of these parties are
aligned with us, honest, in all honesty. However, there is no way for us to, um, however, what ends
up happening in that failure to be out of alignment is that we end up kind of like playing both sides
and we should be playing no sides, right? Off sides. Soccer. So, you know, y'all be talking about
coming at politicians. There's no such thing as coming at politicians. Politicians should be working
for you. That should be their only purpose and their only job. And somehow y'all have made these
niggas celebrities that are impervious to challenge. And I don't know when you all got the idea that
they're not activists because they're supposed to be political activists as black people.
I'm not sure how that continues to get worse and worse and worse, but it is, it is incensing.
I'm going to go because if I don't go to bed tonight at a reasonable hour, it's just not going to be
good for anybody. Like I have to go to bed no later than 10 30. Like I have to do it. So everybody,
you learned a lot. Um, you said Kamala Harris worked for you. I'm not sure in what form or fashion she
did because the argument is always that she has no power and she couldn't do anything. So I'm not sure
what she did for you. I'm not even sure why we want somebody in office that can't do nothing. That don't
make no sense to me. We would have been better off having a white man that's actually got values if it
meant they were going to do something. Um, if it means having a black woman there who can't do
anything. So I don't, I don't understand that logic. In my, in my opinion, all of them are murderers,
serial killers, imperialists, capitalists, all of them. Okay. All of them. Cause that's what the
United States is. And a lot of y'all won't admit to yourselves that you're okay.